Imagine after what happened June 2020 with George Floyd that Black students at universities had to hide and be locked in libraries because white protesters and students and teachers were trying to attack them for being Black.
Someone wrote this and thought they ate.
There's so many things here.
Okay, one.
Some people are saying that Israelis and Jewish people are not the same thing.
And then you have other people who are saying that a critique of Israel is a critique of Jewish people.
So I feel like the conflation is happening from within, not from the outside.
Two, Israel is the oppressor.
Israel is Derek Chauvin in this situation.
So much so that Israeli police are actually who taught Derek Chauvin how to do the move that he used to actually kill George Floyd.
So, yeah, I don't.
What's actually genuinely terrible about this is that it is the actions of the Israeli government that are sowing the seeds of anti-Semitism in this particular situation.
And there are people who are not going to make the discernment between the fact that there are Jewish people that live all over the world that are like loving, incredible people that in no way support what is happening in the genocide in Palestine.
There are also Jewish people who feel like they are akin to whatever is happening in Israel by the nature of its connection to Jewish people and thus feel akin to its government.
So that is a very difficult path to navigate, but it is not a fair generalization to say that one group and the other group are the same group because they're just not.
But when Israel's government makes that generalization, they put all Jewish people in danger of anti-Semitism.
The reality is that it is unacceptable to support a genocide of a people, particularly in the name of a protection of another people.
That's the rub.
That's where the two get conflated.
There are genocides happening all over this world and it's unacceptable.
It is deplorable that there is a genocide happening in the Congo, the Uyghurs in China, the Rohingya in India, the people of South Sudan.
I mean, those are the ones I only know about.
But when we put messages up here like this, what happens is that there's a disconnect from identifying the role that a group is playing in oppressing another group.
And then they are playing a victim role and trying to correlate that to another group that is very clearly the victims.
And what's so frustrating about that is that then it prevents there being actual accountability, which is what causes solution.
Being challenged for views that harm others is not hatred for your faith or your ethnicity.
It is criticism and it is critique.
There are people who spew hatred and they are deplorable.
There are others who provide true queries about why and they should be heard.